desihotstuff.com 2010-04-26

# Desi Hot Stuff » Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while you are online at Desi Hot Stuff. ([bharatbytes.com](http://desihotstuff.com/))

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log**

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscriptions**

If you subscribe to our posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users� privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site uses cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of our advertisers use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission to them to set cookies for advertising.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information ( **not** including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We allow and use outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to these information. We work with the following ad companies: [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/privacypolicy.html). Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

We also allow advertisers and webmasters to place an ad directly by contacting us. We take no responsibility of the content on those sites.

**Note**

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, you can use this [contact form](http://www.bharatbytes.com/?page_id=82) to contact us.
